(Howard:)Preparing to fire laser at the moon.
SHELDON:
Make it so.
(Howard:)There it is. There's the spike.
Two-point-five seconds for the light to
return. That's the moon. We hit the moon.
(Zack:)That's your big experiment?
All that for a line on the screen?
Yeah, but think
about what this represents.
(Leonard:)The fact that we can do this
is the only way of definitively proving...
(Leonard:)...that there are man-made objects
on the moon...
...put there by a species
that only 60 years before...
(Leonard:)...had just invented the airplane.
(Zack:)What species is that?
(Sheldon:)I was wrong. Penny can do better.
(Penny:)-Okay, guys, thank you. It's been fun.
-Yeah, thanks.
(Zack:)-Should we invite them to the party?
-No, just keep walking.
He's must be very skilled at coitus.